<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<interface xmlns="http://www.masagroup.net/directia/schemas/bm" name="properties.Transportable" source-version="1.0.0" extends="properties.Loadable">
    <description>This element represents all units which troops can be transported from one position to another. In sword, the transportation of troops is managed within a specific simulation module. The agent can transports units by adding them to the 'units to transport' via the method &quot;addToTransport&quot;.  Then, the agent makes as many round trips it is necessary to transports the units troops to the destination (to transport troops or specific components of one unit, the agent can perform many round trips, depending on data defined in authoring tool; see the 'Cargo transport' data in 'Equipements ' section).&#xD;
 All elements of the world that realize this interface can be transported or heliported. To transport a unit, the agent needs to have the adpated capacity regarding to component to load (a rifle man within a infantry platoon won't be able to load a vehicle).</description>
    <methods>
        <method name="addToTransport">
            <description>Notify the simulation the 'unit' must be transported. </description>
        </method>
        <method name="readyForBeingTransported">
            <description>Returns 'true' if  the agent is ready to be transported, 'false' otherwise.</description>
            <argument name="distanceMin">
                <description>The minimum distance (in meters) underneath which this element is considered as being ready to get transported by the agent.</description>
                <type>
                    <simple name="numeric"/>
                </type>
            </argument>
            <return>
                <type>
                    <simple name="boolean"/>
                </type>
            </return>
        </method>
        <method name="canTransportIt">
            <description>Returns 'true' if this element can transported, depending on its physical capabilities, 'false' otherwise.</description>
            <argument name="onlyLoadable">
                <description>Define if the transport is made on loadable components (components that are defined as &quot;loadable&quot; within the authoring tool, as 'soldiers' are loadable in their 'armored vehicles') or on other components (as &quot;vehicles&quot;). To simulate troops transportation, this element should be set to 'true', else it should be set to 'false' (helitrasnport for instance).</description>
                <type>
                    <simple name="boolean"/>
                </type>
            </argument>
            <return>
                <type>
                    <simple name="boolean"/>
                </type>
            </return>
        </method>
    </methods>
</interface>